(Raj:)I say we wait until he looks at us,
then laugh like:
"Yes, you are a smart
and strong competitor.
(Raj:)But we are also smart and strong...
(Raj:)...and we have a reasonable chance
of defeating you."
(Leonard:)How exactly would that laugh go?
Hee-hee-hee!
That sounds more like:
"We are a tall, thin woman who wants
to make a coat out of your dalmatians."
(Leonard:)Guys, let's remember that Sheldon
is still our friend and my roommate.
(Howard:)So?
(Leonard:)So nothing. Let's destroy him.
SHELDON:
Gentlemen.
RAJESH:
Hee-hee-hee!
Okay, we're gonna need a strong fourth
for our team.
You know who is apparently very smart
is the girl who played TV's Blossom.
(Raj:)She got a Ph.D. in neuroscience
or something.
(Leonard:)Raj, we're not getting TV's Blossom
to join our Physics Bowl team.